

6

+(60) 018-9165768



cheryiong62@gmail.com



Penang, Malaysia



https://github.com/KevinLim62



www.linkedin.com/in/kevinlim62



https://kevin62-portfolio.vercel.app/

PROFILE

A very self-disciplined, resultoriented full stack developer with demonstrated experience in building CRM system, blockchain related authenticity verification system. I able to communicate effectively in English, Chinese and Malay in both spoken and written forms.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR IN MECHATRONICS ENGINEERING

May 2017 - May 2021

University Tunku Abdul Rahman

Grade: CGPA 3.59 / 4.0

SKILLS

- Frontend stacks: Reactjs, Nextjs, TailwindCSS, ShadcnUI
- Backend stacks: Nodejs, Expressjs, Nestjs, TypeORM, Mongoose
- Databases: MongoDB, PostgreSQL
- Languages: JavaScript, Typescript
- APIs: REST, GraphQL
- Clouds / Containers: AWS, Vercel, Docker, Render

CERTIFICATIONS

AWS Cloud Quest: Cloud Practitioner

Kevin Lim Cher Yiong

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Blockchain Solution Pte Ltd

Jun 2023 - Present

- Developed responsive UI interfaces using Nextjs, TailwindCSS & Typescript.
- Developed backend API and created database aggregation pipeline to serve data using Nodejs, Expressjs & MongoDB.
- Performed application testing, debugging and fixing bugs for quality assurance.
- Worked within an agile scrum team, contributing to 100% continuous improvement and deployment.

Authenticity Verification System

- Developed SaaS product to provide comprehensive blockchain verification and authenticity for brands.
- Enhanced page loading speed by 40% using React lazy loading and suspense techniques.
- Implemented features such as loyalty system to improve end user engagement, resulted in increment of client subscriptions.
- Leveraged AI chatbot to provide responses to customer queries.

Customer Relationship Management Dashboard

- Developed CRM dashboard catering to brand clients, offers insightful analytics on sales performance and end user geographical distribution.
- Built features of comprehensive CRUD functionality for product, batch and provenance alongside with report generation and admin management.
- Leveraged database aggregation pipeline code for responsive data visualization dashboard.

Artwork Gallery

• Provided reusable functions including Gif file generator for NFT, artwork image comparison view generator, bulk artworks upload script.

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER

Donjon Fauna Indie Game Studio

Jul 2023 - Aug 202

- Built single page application using React framework and Typescript.
- Reduced page loading speed by 20% using cached images and videos at Cloudinary CDN.
- Developed a demo of development log application for storing development notes using markdown.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER Greatech Technology Berhad

Jul 2021 - Jun 2023

- Executed PLC programming (Siemens & Allen Bradley), motion control and configuration on motor (Siemens, Festo & PBA), and robot programming (Fanuc & Epson).
- Led a team of 4 in RnD project Vial Inspection Module, improved machine cycle time and part per minute by 20%.
- Co-led in Fanuc robot training class to internal engineers.
- Conducted machine validation at Boston Scientific.

INTERN TRAINEE (SOFTWARE & TECHNICAL TEAM) Solo Labeller Technology Oct 2019 - Dec 2019

- Performed data fetching and sorting on Google Sheet using Google Apps Script.
- Developed a dashboard web application using HTML, CSS, and Javascript, visualized machine production data and deployed on Google server.